Mapillary Privacy Policy
------------------------

Effective date: February 15, 2024

This Privacy Policy explains how Mapillary, offered by Meta Platforms Ireland Limited (“Mapillary,” “we,” or “us”) collect, use, and share information about you. This Privacy Policy applies when you use the Mapillary websites, mobile applications, and other online products and services (collectively, our “Services”), or otherwise interact with us.

This Privacy Policy changes from time to time. When we make changes, we will notify you by revising the date at the top of this policy and, in some cases where we materially change how we use your personal data, we will provide you with additional notice (such as adding a statement to our website or sending you a notification). We encourage you to review this Privacy Policy regularly to stay informed about our information practices and the choices available to you.

### Table of Contents

1. [Imagery Collected and Shared by Users via our Services](https://www.mapillary.com/privacy#imagery)
2. [Collection of Information](https://www.mapillary.com/privacy#collection)
3. [Use of Information](https://www.mapillary.com/privacy#information)
4. [Sharing of Information](https://www.mapillary.com/privacy#sharing)
5. [Legal Basis for Processing](https://www.mapillary.com/privacy#legal)
6. [Data Retention](https://www.mapillary.com/privacy#retention)
7. [Transfer of Information to the United States and Other Countries](https://www.mapillary.com/privacy#transfer)
8. [Your Rights and Choices](https://www.mapillary.com/privacy#rights)
9. [Contact Us](https://www.mapillary.com/privacy#contact)

### Imagery Collected and Shared by Users via our Services

We offer our users tools to collect and upload street-level imagery to our Services.

We use technology designed to blur any faces and license plates our algorithms detect within the imagery to help reduce privacy impact. Following this process, the imagery is typically published via our Services for other users to use in accordance with our [terms](https://www.mapillary.com/terms).

Our terms require users to notify us if they observe any imagery on the Services that may contain personal data. If you detect any potential privacy concerns with any of the imagery available via the Services, please contact us at [support@mapillary.zendesk.com](mailto:support@mapillary.zendesk.com).

### Collection of Information

Information You Provide to Us

We collect information you provide directly to us about yourself. For example, you share information directly with us when you create an account, provide mapping content or other content through our Services, participate in our forums, comment on or flag content posted by other users, participate in a challenge, download content (such as a research data set), request support, comment on our blog posts, or otherwise communicate with us. The types of information we may collect about you include your name, email address, account credentials, postal address, phone number, profile photo, profile bio, and any other information you choose to provide.

Information We Collect Automatically When You Use our Services

When you access or use our Services, we automatically collect certain information about you, including:

* Device and Activity Information: We collect information about how you access our Services, including data about the device and network you use, such as your hardware model, operating system version, mobile network, IP address, unique device identifiers, browser type, and app version. We also collect information about your activity on our Services, such as the time and date you access our Services, which content you have uploaded, pages viewed, links clicked, and the page you visited before navigating to our Services.
    
* Location Information: In accordance with the permissions you set on your device, we may collect information about the precise location of your device. You may stop the collection of precise location information at any time (see the Your Choices section below for details). We may infer your approximate location based on your IP address.
    
* Stored Information: We may access information you have stored on your mobile device via our mobile applications in accordance with permission settings you set on your mobile device. For example, with your permission, we may access photos or videos from your mobile device photo gallery.
    
* Information Collected by Cookies and Similar Tracking Technologies: We (and our service providers) use tracking technologies, such as cookies and web beacons, to collect information about you. For more information about cookies and how to disable them, see our [Cookie Policy](https://www.mapillary.com/cookies) and the Your Choices section below.

Information We Collect from Other Sources

We obtain information from third-party sources. For example, if you create or log into your Mapillary account through another platform (such as Facebook or Google), we will have access to certain information from that platform, such as your profile photo and language preference, in accordance with the authorization procedures determined by such platform.

### Use of Information

We use the information we collect to:

* Provide, maintain, and improve our products and services, including to improve the technology and algorithms that power our Services, and to develop new products and services;
    
* Personalize and improve your experience on our Services;
    
* Send you technical notices, security alerts, and support and administrative messages;
    
* Respond to your comments and questions and investigate content flagged by users;
    
* Communicate with you about products, services, and events we or others offer and provide information that we think will interest you (see Your Choices below for information about how to opt out of promotional emails);
    
* Monitor and analyze trends, usage, and activities in connection with our Services;
    
* Facilitate contests, challenges, sweepstakes, and promotions and process and deliver entries and rewards;
    
* Detect, investigate, and prevent security incidents and other malicious, deceptive, fraudulent, or illegal activity and protect the rights and property of Mapillary and others;
    
* Debug to identify and repair errors in our Services;
    
* Comply with our legal and financial obligations; and
    
* Carry out any other purpose described to you at the time the information was collected.

### Sharing of Information

We share information about you in the following circumstances or as otherwise described in this policy:

* With vendors, service providers, and affiliates (as specified below) that perform services for us, such as companies that assist us with web hosting, image blurring, annotation and processing, email delivery, and customer service. Such sharing occurs between and among Mapillary and our current and future parents, affiliates, and subsidiaries, and other companies under common control and ownership.
    
* If we believe that disclosure is in accordance with, or required by, any applicable law or legal process, including lawful requests by public authorities to meet national security or law enforcement requirements.
    
* If we believe that your actions are inconsistent with our user agreements or policies, or if we believe it is necessary to protect the rights, property, and safety of Mapillary or others.
    
* In connection with, or during negotiations concerning, any merger, sale of company assets, financing, or acquisition of all or a portion of our business by another company.
    
* With your consent or at your direction. For example, if you submit imagery or post content in a public area of our Services, we share this information (such as through our APIs or publicly on our Services). Additionally, if you choose to use integrations we offer on our Services, we may share certain information with the integration partners, including Mapbox and OpenStreetMap.

We also share aggregated or de-identified information that cannot reasonably be used to identify you.

### Legal Basis for Processing

When we process your personal data, we do so in reliance on the following lawful bases:

* To perform our responsibilities under our contract with you (e.g., to provide image datasets for research use or other products and services you request).
    
* When we have a legitimate interest in processing your personal data to operate our business or protect our interests (e.g., to provide, maintain, and improve our products and services, including our blurring algorithms, to develop new products and services, conduct data analytics, and communicate with you).
    
* To comply with our legal obligations (e.g., to maintain a record of your consents).
    
* When we have your consent to do so (e.g., when you opt in to receive marketing communications from us). When consent is the legal basis for processing your personal data, you may withdraw such consent at any time.

### Data Retention

We will retain content you have posted to the Services (like imagery you share, forum posts, or comments you post about other users’ content), but upon request, we can remove your username and other identifying information from this retained content. We store other personal data for as long as necessary to carry out the purposes for which we originally collected it and for other legitimate business purposes, including to meet our compliance obligations.

### Transfer of Information to the United States and Other Countries

We may process Information on servers located in a number of countries. We will only transfer personal data from the European Economic Area (EEA), the United Kingdom, or Switzerland to a third country, pursuant to a data transfer mechanism authorized under applicable law. For example, we provide adequate protection for the transfer of personal data originating from those countries to third countries (such as the U.S.) through a series of intercompany agreements based on the Standard Contractual Clauses. You may request a copy of the legal safeguards we have put in place to safeguard your transferred personal data by contacting us at [privacy@mapillary.com](mailto:privacy@mapillary.com) .

### Your Rights and Choices

Data Subject Rights

Subject to certain limitations, you have the right to request: information about how we process your personal data; access to a copy of the personal data we hold about you; to receive your data in a portable format; withdrawal of any consent you have previously provided us; that your personal data be corrected or erased. Subject to certain limitations, you also have the right to object to, or request that we restrict, certain processing. If you would like to exercise any of these rights, please email us at [privacy@mapillary.com](mailto:privacy@mapillary.com) .

If you have a concern about our processing of personal data that we are not able to resolve, you may have the right to lodge a complaint with the Data Protection Authority where you reside. Contact details for your Data Protection Authority can be found using the links below:

### United States Residents

You can learn more about the consumer privacy rights that may be available to you by reviewing the [United States Regional Privacy Notice](https://www.mapillary.com/privacy/united-states).

Your Choices

* Account Information: You may update and correct certain account profile information at any time by logging into your account. If you wish to delete your account, please contact us at [support@mapillary.zendesk.com](mailto:support@mapillary.zendesk.com). Please note that we may retain certain information following account deletion as required or permitted by law, such as for our legitimate business purposes.
    
* Location Information: If you initially consent to our collection of location information through our mobile app, you can subsequently stop the collection of this information at any time by changing the preferences on your mobile device or removing all of our mobile apps from your device. If you stop our collection of this location information, some features of our Services may no longer function properly.
    
* Cookies: Most web browsers are set to accept cookies by default. If you prefer, you can usually adjust your browser settings to remove or reject browser cookies. Please note that removing or rejecting cookies could affect the availability and functionality of our Services. For more information about cookies and how to disable them, see our [Cookie Policy](https://www.mapillary.com/cookies).
    
* Communications Preferences: You may opt out of receiving promotional emails from Mapillary by following the instructions in those communications. You may also control the other types of emails and mobile push notifications (if you consented to receive push notifications) we send to you by adjusting the notification preferences in the settings menu in your account.

### Contact Us

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us at [privacy@mapillary.com](mailto:privacy@mapillary.com) .

### Apps

### GIS solutions

### Developers

### Resources

### About

### Legal

### Connect

© 2024 Mapillary from Meta
